<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://fluffsec.github.io/fluffsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-08-04T13:43:48.788Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://fluffsec.github.io/fluffsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://fluffsec.github.io/fluffsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ping Identity to Go Private After $2.8B Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/ping-identity-to-go-public-acquisition</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/ping-identity-to-go-public-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T13:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The identity-services company is being acquired by Thoma Bravo software investment for cash, before being delisted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Woody RAT Malware Being Used to Target Russian Organizations]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-6273595063188687046</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/new-woody-rat-malware-being-used-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T12:55:40.090Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor has been targeting Russian entities with a newly discovered remote access trojan called Woody RAT for at least a year as part of a spear-phishing campaign.
The advanced custom backdoor is said to be delivered via either of two methods: archive files and Microsoft Office documents leveraging the now-patched "Follina" support diagnostic tool vulnerability (CVE-2022-30190)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KnowBe4 Wins Multiple Summer 2022 "Best of" Awards From TrustRadius]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/knowbe4-wins-multiple-summer-2022-best-of-awards-from-trustradius</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/knowbe4-wins-multiple-summer-2022-best-of-awards-from-trustradius"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KnowBe4 is proud to be recognized by TrustRadius with the Summer Best of Awards in three categories for the Security Awareness Training software category.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Common Mistakes That May Sabotage Your Security Training]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1366682569617480816</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/three-common-mistakes-that-may-sabotage.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T10:37:07.795Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing incidents are on the rise. A report from IBM shows that phishing was the most popular attack vector in 2021, resulting in one in five employees falling victim to phishing hacking techniques.
The Need for Security Awareness Training 
Although technical solutions protect against phishing threats, no solution is 100% effective. Consequently, companies have no choice but to involve their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploited Atlassian Confluence Bug to Deploy Ljl Backdoor for Espionage]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-78825967950418576</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/hackers-exploited-atlassian-confluence.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T10:24:10.616Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor is said to have "highly likely" exploited a security flaw in an outdated Atlassian Confluence server to deploy a never-before-seen backdoor against an unnamed organization in the research and technical services sector.
The attack, which transpired over a seven-day-period during the end of May, has been attributed to a threat activity cluster tracked by cybersecurity firm Deepwatch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Business Routers Found Vulnerable to Critical Remote Hacking Flaws]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3081742026568892649</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/cisco-business-routers-found-vulnerable.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T05:11:25.400Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco on Wednesday rolled out patches to address eight security vulnerabilities, three of which could be weaponized by an unauthenticated attacker to gain remote code execution (RCE) or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on affected devices.
The most critical of the flaws impact Cisco Small Business RV160, RV260, RV340, and RV345 Series routers. Tracked as CVE-2022-20842 (CVSS score: 9.8)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Startup Footprint Tackles Identity Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/new-startup-footprint-tackles-identity-verification</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/new-startup-footprint-tackles-identity-verification"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T23:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early-stage startup Footprint's goal is to provide tools that change how enterprises verify, authentication, authorize, and secure identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IT Teams Can Use 'Harm Reduction' for Better Cybersecurity Outcomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/teams-harm-reduction-better-cybersecurity-outcomes</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/teams-harm-reduction-better-cybersecurity-outcomes"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T21:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copado's Kyle Tobener will discuss a three-pronged plan at Black Hat USA for addressing human weaknesses in cybersecurity with this medical concept — from phishing to shadow IT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical RCE Bug in DrayTek Routers Opens SMBs to Zero-Click Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/critical-rce-bug-draytek-routers-smbs-zero-click-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/critical-rce-bug-draytek-routers-smbs-zero-click-attacks"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T20:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SMBs should patch CVE-2022-32548 now to avoid a host of horrors, including complete network compromise, ransomware, state-sponsored attacks, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[School Kid Uploads Ransomware Scripts to PyPI Repository as 'Fun' Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/school-kid-uploads-ransomware-scripts-to-pypi-repository-as-fun-research-project</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/school-kid-uploads-ransomware-scripts-to-pypi-repository-as-fun-research-project"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T19:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The malware packages had names that were common typosquats of a legitimate widely used Python library. One was downloaded hundreds of times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Spotlight: Vulnerabilities in Alyac antivirus program could stop virus scanning, cause code execution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/05/vuln-spotlight-alyac-est.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/05/vuln-spotlight-alyac-est.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T18:46:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jaewon Min of Cisco Talos discovered these vulnerabilities. Blog by Jon Munshaw. 
Update (Aug. 3, 2022): Talos disclosed two new vulnerabilities in the Alyac antivirus software and added their details to this post.
Cisco Talos recently discovered out-of-bounds read and buffer overflow vulnerabilities in ESTsecurity Corp.’s Alyac antivirus software that could cause a denial-of-service condition or arbitrary code execution. Alyac is an antivirus software developed for Microsoft Windows machines. 
TALOS-2022-1452 (CVE-2022-21147) is a vulnerability that exists in a specific Alyac module that, eventually, leads to a crash of Alyac’s scanning process, which effectively neutralizes the antivirus scan. If successful, an attacker could trigger this vulnerability to stop the program from scanning for malware, which would be crucial in a potential attack scenario. 
TALOS-2022-1527 (CVE-2022-32543) and TALOS-2022-1533 (CVE-2022-29886) are heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities that an attacker could exploit to execute arbitrary code on the targeted machine. The adversary would have to convince a user to open a specially crafted OLE file to trigger this condition.

Cisco Talos worked with ESTsecurity to ensure that these issues are resolved and an update is available for affected customers, all in adherence to Cisco’s vulnerability disclosure policy. 


Users are encouraged to update these affected products as soon as possible: ESTsoft Alyac, versions 2.5.7.7 and 2.5.8.544. Talos tested and confirmed ESTsoft Alyac, version 2.5.7.7, is affected by TALOS-2022-1452. Version 2.5.8.544 is vulnerable to TALOS-2022-1533 and TALOS-2022-1527.


The following Snort rules will detect exploitation attempts against these vulnerabilities: 59014, 59015, and 60035 - 60042. Additional rules may be released in the future and current rules are subject to change, pending additional vulnerability information. For the most current rule information, please refer to your Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center or Snort.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cisco Talos Intelligence Group - Comprehensive Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers Drain Nearly $6M From Solana Crypto Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cyberattackers-drain-6m-solana-crypto-wallets</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cyberattackers-drain-6m-solana-crypto-wallets"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T17:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So far, the ongoing attack has impacted nearly 8,000 Solana hot wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Single-Core CPU Cracked Post-Quantum Encryption Candidate Algorithm in Just an Hour]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-754771862655875762</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/single-core-cpu-cracked-post-quantum.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T17:01:11.109Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A late-stage candidate encryption algorithm that was meant to withstand decryption by powerful quantum computers in the future has been trivially cracked by using a computer running Intel Xeon CPU in an hour's time.
The algorithm in question is SIKE — short for Supersingular Isogeny Key Encapsulation — which made it to the fourth round of the Post-Quantum Cryptography (PQC) standardization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Day Defense: Tips for Defusing the Threat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/zero-day-defense-tips-for-defusing-the-threat</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/zero-day-defense-tips-for-defusing-the-threat"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because they leave so little time to patch and defuse, zero-day threats require a proactive, multilayered approach based on zero trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Barnett, Principal Security Researcher, Akamai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ShiftLeft Appoints Prevention-First, Cybersecurity Visionary and AI/ML Pioneer Stuart McClure as CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/shiftleft-appoints-prevention-first-cybersecurity-visionary-and-ai-ml-pioneer-stuart-mcclure-as-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/shiftleft-appoints-prevention-first-cybersecurity-visionary-and-ai-ml-pioneer-stuart-mcclure-as-ceo"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serial entrepreneur, cybersecurity leader, and industry veteran joins ShiftLeft to drive growth and AI/ML innovation globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Druva Introduces the Data Resiliency Guarantee of up to $10 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/druva-introduces-the-data-resiliency-guarantee-of-up-to-10-million</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/druva-introduces-the-data-resiliency-guarantee-of-up-to-10-million"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new program offers robust protection across all five data risk categories: cyber, human, application, operation, and environmental.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Demand Webinar: New 2022 Phishing By Industry Benchmarking Report: How Does Your Organization Measure Up]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/2022-phishing-by-industry-benchmarking-webinar</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/2022-phishing-by-industry-benchmarking-webinar"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a security leader, you have a lot on your plate. Even as you increase your budget for sophisticated security software, your exposure to cybercrime keeps going up. IT security seems to be a race between effective technology and ever evolving attack strategies from the threat actors. However, there’s an often-overlooked security layer that can significantly reduce your organization’s attack surface: New-school security awareness training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMWare Urges Users to Patch Critical Authentication Bypass Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180346</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/vmware-patch-critical-bug/180346/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability—for which a proof-of-concept is forthcoming—is one of a string of flaws the company fixed that could lead to an attack chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CompTIA CEO Outlines Initiative to Create the Pre-eminent Destination to Start, Build and ‘Supercharge’ a Tech Career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/comptia-ceo-outlines-initiative-to-create-the-pre-eminent-destination-to-start-build-and-supercharge-a-tech-career</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/comptia-ceo-outlines-initiative-to-create-the-pre-eminent-destination-to-start-build-and-supercharge-a-tech-career"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Todd Thibodeaux uses ChannelCon 2022 state of the industry remarks to unveil CompTIA’s Project Agora; invites broad industry participation in the effort to fight for tech talent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases Security Updates]]></title>
        <id>17842 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/08/03/vmware-releases-security-updates-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: August 3, 2022
VMware has released security updates to address multiple vulnerabilities in VMware’s Workspace ONE Access, Access Connector, Identity Manager, Identity Manager Connector, and vRealize Automation. A remote attacker could exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system. 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review VMware Security Advisory VMSA-2022-0021 and apply the necessary updates. 

 
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netskope Acquires Infiot, Will Deliver Fully Integrated, Single-Vendor SASE Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/netskope-acquires-infiot-will-deliver-fully-integrated-single-vendor-sase-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/netskope-acquires-infiot-will-deliver-fully-integrated-single-vendor-sase-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T14:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Converged SASE platform provides AI-driven Zero trust security and simplified, optimized connectivity to any network location or device, including IoT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways Chess Can Inspire Strategic Cybersecurity Thinking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/5-ways-chess-can-inspire-strategic-cybersecurity-thinking</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/5-ways-chess-can-inspire-strategic-cybersecurity-thinking"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising interest in chess may feed the next generation of cybersecurity experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miki Shifman, CTO and Co-Founder, Cylus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Express, Snapchat Open-Redirect Vulnerabilities Exploited in Phishing Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/american-express-snapchat-open-redirect-vulnerabilities-exploited-phishing</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/american-express-snapchat-open-redirect-vulnerabilities-exploited-phishing"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T13:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing operators are taking advantage of security bugs in the Amex and Snapchat websites (the latter is unpatched) to steer victims to phishing pages looking to harvest Google and Microsoft logins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labor Market Social Engineering: Supply-Side and Demand-Side]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/labor-market-social-engineering-supply-side-and-demand-side</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/labor-market-social-engineering-supply-side-and-demand-side"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T12:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re accustomed to social engineering being used for credential theft and business email compromise. We’re also accustomed to hearing about the increase in remote work during the pandemic, and how that has expanded organizations’ attack surface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Data Breach Extortion Attack Begins with a Fake Duolingo or MasterClass Subscription Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/new-data-breach-extortion-attack-begins-with-a-fake-duolingo-or-masterclass-subscription-scam</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/new-data-breach-extortion-attack-begins-with-a-fake-duolingo-or-masterclass-subscription-scam"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T12:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cybercriminal gang, dubbed ‘Luna Moth’ uses a sophisticated mix of phishing, vishing, remote support sessions, and remote access trojans to gain control of victim endpoints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirusTotal Reveals Most Impersonated Software in Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1835752372760943731</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/virustotal-reveals-most-impersonated.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T12:36:55.831Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are increasingly mimicking legitimate applications like Skype, Adobe Reader, and VLC Player as a means to abuse trust relationships and increase the likelihood of a successful social engineering attack.
Other most impersonated legitimate apps by icon include 7-Zip, TeamViewer, CCleaner, Microsoft Edge, Steam, Zoom, and WhatsApp, an analysis from VirusTotal has revealed.
"One of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Demand Webinar: New CISO Survey Reveals Top Challenges for Small Cyber Security Teams]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-8047985041763007295</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/on-demand-webinar-new-ciso-survey.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T12:13:12.632Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only threat more persistent to organizations than cyber criminals? The cyber security skills crisis. 
Nearly 60% of enterprises can’t find the staff to protect their data (and reputations!) from new and emerging breeds of cyber-attacks, reports the Information Systems Security Association (ISSA) in its 5th annual global industry study. 
The result? Heavier workloads, unfilled positions, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Warns of Large-Scale AiTM Attacks Targeting Enterprise Users]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1294765518214243565</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/researchers-warns-of-large-scale-aitm.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T09:03:35.115Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new, large-scale phishing campaign has been observed using adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) techniques to get around security protections and compromise enterprise email accounts.
"It uses an adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) attack technique capable of bypassing multi-factor authentication," Zscaler researchers Sudeep Singh and Jagadeeswar Ramanukolanu said in a Tuesday report. "The campaign is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases Patches for Several New Flaws Affecting Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-868155627775515841</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/vmware-releases-patches-for-several-new.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T04:49:51.482Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization services provider VMware on Tuesday shipped updates to address 10 security flaws affecting multiple products that could be abused by unauthenticated attackers to perform malicious actions.
The issues tracked from CVE-2022-31656 through CVE-2022-31665 (CVSS scores: 4.7 - 9.8) affect the VMware Workspace ONE Access, Workspace ONE Access Connector, Identity Manager, Identity Manager]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universities Put Email Users at Cyber Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180342</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/universities-email-cyber-risk/180342/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DMARC analysis by Proofpoint shows that institutions in the U.S. have among some of the poorest protections to prevent domain spoofing and lack protections to block fraudulent emails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universities Put Email Users at Cyber Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180342</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/universities-email-cyber-risk/180342/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DMARC analysis by Proofpoint shows that institutions in the U.S. have among some of the poorest protections to prevent domain spoofing and lack protections to block fraudulent emails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Mobile Apps Leaking Twitter API Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/thousands-of-mobile-apps-leaking-twitter-api-keys</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/thousands-of-mobile-apps-leaking-twitter-api-keys"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T22:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New finding comes amid report of overall surge in threats targeting mobile and IoT devices over the past year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language AI Models Have Real Security Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/large-language-ai-models-have-real-security-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/large-language-ai-models-have-real-security-benefits"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T22:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Complex neural networks, including GPT-3, can deliver useful cybersecurity capabilities such as explaining malware and quickly classifying websites, researchers find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive New Phishing Campaign Targets Microsoft Email Service Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/massive-new-phishing-campaign-targeting-microsoft-email-users</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/massive-new-phishing-campaign-targeting-microsoft-email-users"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T21:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The campaign uses adversary-in-the-middle techniques to bypass multifactor authentication, evade detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Babuk Source Code to Darkside Custom Listings — Exposing a Thriving Ransomware Marketplace on the Dark Web]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/from-babuk-source-code-to-darkside-custom-listings-exposing-a-thriving-ransomware-marketplace-on-the-dark-web</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/from-babuk-source-code-to-darkside-custom-listings-exposing-a-thriving-ransomware-marketplace-on-the-dark-web"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T20:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venafi investigation of 35 million Dark Web URLs shows macro-enabled ransomware widely available at bargain prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing Sector in 2022 Is More Vulnerable to Account Compromise and Supply Chain Attacks in the Cloud than Other Verticals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/manufacturing-sector-in-2022-is-more-vulnerable-to-account-compromise-and-supply-chain-attacks-in-the-cloud-than-other-verticals</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/manufacturing-sector-in-2022-is-more-vulnerable-to-account-compromise-and-supply-chain-attacks-in-the-cloud-than-other-verticals"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T20:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netwrix study reveals that manufacturing organizations experienced these types of attacks more often than any other industry surveyed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axis Raises the Bar With Modern-Day ZTNA Service that Boasts Hyper-Intelligence, Simplicity, and 350 Global Edges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/axis-raises-the-bar-with-modern-day-ztna-service-that-boasts-hyper-intelligence-simplicity-and-350-global-edges</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/axis-raises-the-bar-with-modern-day-ztna-service-that-boasts-hyper-intelligence-simplicity-and-350-global-edges"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T19:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launches industry’s first ZTNA migration tool and ZTNA buyback program, setting the stage for migration away from ZTNA 1.0.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security and Gender: The Gaps Are Not Where You Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/security-and-gender-the-gaps-are-not-where-you-expect</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/security-and-gender-the-gaps-are-not-where-you-expect"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T18:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 KnowBe4 Women’s Day Survey interviewed more than 200 women from across the technology industry in South Africa to find out more about how they perceive the industry, the gender gap and discrimination. The survey focused on some of the key challenges traditionally experienced by women in the IT and technology sectors and interviewed women ranging in age from 25-54.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Collard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile Store Owner Made $25M Using Stolen Employee Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/t-mobile-store-owner-made-25m-with-stolen-employee-credentials</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/t-mobile-store-owner-made-25m-with-stolen-employee-credentials"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T18:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now-convicted phone dealer reset locked and blocked phones on various mobile networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Intros New Attack Surface Management, Threat Intel Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/microsoft-intros-threat-intel-attack-surface-management-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/microsoft-intros-threat-intel-attack-surface-management-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T17:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says the new tools will give security teams an attacker's-eye view of their systems and supercharge their investigation and remediation efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One Breach Conviction Exposes Scale of Cloud Entitlement Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/capital-one-breach-conviction-exposes-scale-of-cloud-entitlement-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/capital-one-breach-conviction-exposes-scale-of-cloud-entitlement-risk"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To protect against similar attacks, organizations should focus on bringing cloud entitlements and configurations under control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shai Morag, CEO, Ermetic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Using New Manjusaka Hacking Framework Similar to Cobalt Strike]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-8191798645489120302</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/chinese-hackers-using-new-manjusaka.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T16:03:45.104Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have disclosed a new offensive framework called Manjusaka that they call a "Chinese sibling of Sliver and Cobalt Strike."
"A fully functional version of the command-and-control (C2), written in GoLang with a User Interface in Simplified Chinese, is freely available and can generate new implants with custom configurations with ease, increasing the likelihood of wider adoption of this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirusTotal: Threat Actors Mimic Legitimate Apps, Use Stolen Certs to Spread Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/virustotal-threat-actors-mimic-legitimate-apps-use-stolen-certs-to-spread-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/virustotal-threat-actors-mimic-legitimate-apps-use-stolen-certs-to-spread-malware"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are turning to stolen credentials and posing as trusted applications to socially engineer victims, according to Google study of malware submitted to VirusTotal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incognia Mobile App Study Reveals Low Detection of Location Spoofing in Dating Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/incognia-mobile-app-study-reveals-low-detection-of-location-spoofing-in-dating-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/incognia-mobile-app-study-reveals-low-detection-of-location-spoofing-in-dating-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T15:24:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With over 323 million users of dating apps worldwide, study finds location spoofing is a threat to user trust and safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackCloak Bolsters Malware Protection With QR Code Scanner and Malicious Calendar Detection Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/mobile/blackcloak-bolsters-malware-protection-with-qr-code-scanner-and-malicious-calendar-detection-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/mobile/blackcloak-bolsters-malware-protection-with-qr-code-scanner-and-malicious-calendar-detection-features"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T14:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conjunction with Black Hat 2022, pioneer of digital executive protection also announces new security innovations and SOC 2 Type II certification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybrary Lands $25 Million in New Funding Round]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/cybrary-lands-25-million-in-new-funding-round</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/cybrary-lands-25-million-in-new-funding-round"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T14:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Series C investment from BuildGroup and Gula Tech Adventures, along with appointment of Kevin Mandia to the board of directors, will propel a new chapter of company growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Steps to Becoming Secure by Design in the Face of Evolving Cyber Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/5-steps-to-becoming-secure-by-design-in-the-face-of-evolving-cyber-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/5-steps-to-becoming-secure-by-design-in-the-face-of-evolving-cyber-threats"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From adopting zero-trust security models to dynamic environments to operating under an "assumed breach" mentality, here are ways IT departments can reduce vulnerabilities as they move deliberately to become more secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sudhakar Ramakrishna, CEO, SolarWinds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CREST Defensible Penetration Test Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/crest-defensible-penetration-test-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/crest-defensible-penetration-test-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T13:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CREST provides commercially defensible scoping, delivery, and sign-off
recommendations for penetration tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyberheistNews Vol 12 #31 [Heads Up] Crafty Microsoft USB Scam Shows the Importance of Security Awareness Training]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/cyberheistnews-vol-12-31-heads-up-crafty-microsoft-usb-scam-shows-the-importance-of-security-awareness-training</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/cyberheistnews-vol-12-31-heads-up-crafty-microsoft-usb-scam-shows-the-importance-of-security-awareness-training"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T13:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CyberheistNews Vol 12 #31 [Heads Up] Crafty Microsoft USB Scam Shows the Importance of Security Awareness Training]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Insurance Expected to Continue to Rise as Sophistication and Cost of Ransomware Attacks Increase]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/cyber-insurance-expected-to-continue-to-rise-as-sophistication-and-cost-of-ransomware-attacks-increase</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/cyber-insurance-expected-to-continue-to-rise-as-sophistication-and-cost-of-ransomware-attacks-increase"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T13:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New data about the state of cyber insurance shows that given the current loss ratios by insurers – and the reasons behind those losses – will result in higher premiums for the foreseeable future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experian Customer “Impersonation” Account Takeover Uncovered by KrebsOnSecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/experian-customer-impersonation-account-takeover-uncovered-by-krebsonsecurity</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/experian-customer-impersonation-account-takeover-uncovered-by-krebsonsecurity"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T13:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a few notifications of a potential problem with Experian by his readership, Brian Krebs and team checked out Experian’s account signup process and found some disturbing news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'ParseThru' Parameter Smuggling Vulnerability Affects Golang-based Applications]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-2640778599302498629</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/new-parsethru-parameter-smuggling.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T12:05:19.919Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have discovered a new vulnerability called ParseThru affecting Golang-based applications that could be abused to gain unauthorized access to cloud-based applications.
"The newly discovered vulnerability allows a threat actor to bypass validations under certain conditions, as a result of the use of unsafe URL parsing methods built in the language," Israeli cybersecurity firm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is ransomware and how can you defend your business from it?]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-170786089995789313</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/what-is-ransomware-how-to-defend-your.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T11:25:05.649Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware is a kind of malware used by cybercriminals to stop users from accessing their systems or files; the cybercriminals then threaten to leak, destroy or withhold sensitive information unless a ransom is paid.
Ransomware attacks can target either the data held on computer systems (known as locker ransomware) or devices (crypto-ransomware). In both instances, once a ransom is paid, threat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware Abuses Windows Defender to Deploy Cobalt Strike Payload]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-6325931217584980108</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/lockbit-ransomware-abuses-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T08:07:34.219Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor associated with the LockBit 3.0 ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation has been observed abusing the Windows Defender command-line tool to decrypt and load Cobalt Strike payloads. 
According to a report published by SentinelOne last week, the incident occurred after obtaining initial access via the Log4Shell vulnerability against an unpatched VMware Horizon Server.
"Once initial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoJ: Foreign Adversaries Breach US Federal Court Records]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/doj-foreign-adversaries-breach-us-federal-court-records</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/doj-foreign-adversaries-breach-us-federal-court-records"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T20:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Justice Department official testifies to a House committee that the cyberattack is a "significant concern."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Hit on European Pipeline & Energy Supplier Encevo Linked to BlackCat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/european-energy-supplier-encevo-breached-in-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/european-energy-supplier-encevo-breached-in-attack"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T19:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers across several European countries are urged to update credentials in the wake of the attack that affected a gas-pipeline operator and power company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Credential Canaries Create Minefield for Attackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/emerging-tech/credential-canaries-create-minefield-for-attackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/emerging-tech/credential-canaries-create-minefield-for-attackers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T18:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canary tokens — also known as honey tokens — force attackers to second-guess their potential good fortune when they come across user and application secrets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromium Browsers Allow Data Exfiltration via Bookmark Syncing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/chromium-browsers-data-exfiltration-bookmark-syncing</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/chromium-browsers-data-exfiltration-bookmark-syncing"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T17:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Bruggling" emerges as a novel technique for pilfering data out from a compromised environment — or for sneaking in malicious code and attack tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name That Edge Toon: Up a Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/name-that-edge-toon-up-a-tree</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/name-that-edge-toon-up-a-tree"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T16:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come up with a clever caption, and our panel of experts will reward the winner with a $25 Amazon gift card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Klossner, Cartoonist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Spotlight: How misusing properly serialized data opened TCL LinkHub Mesh Wi-Fi system to 17 vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/08/vulnerability-spotlight-how-misusing.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/08/vulnerability-spotlight-how-misusing.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T16:18:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Carl Hurd. 
The TCL LinkHub Mesh Wi-Fi system is a multi-device Wi-Fi system that allows users to expand access to their network over a large physical area. What makes the LInkHub system unique is the lack of a network interface to manage the devices individually or in the mesh. Instead, a phone application is the only method to interact with these devices. This is noteworthy because, in theory, it significantly reduces the common attack surface on most small office/home office (SOHO) routers, as it moves the entire HTTP/S code base from the product. This means, in theory, fewer issues with integration or hacked-together scripts to trigger various functions within the device. One of the issues with this approach though is that its functionality still needs to reside somewhere for the us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cisco Talos Intelligence Group - Comprehensive Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Live Demo] Ridiculously Easy Security Awareness Training and Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/live-demo-security-awareness-training-and-phishing</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/live-demo-security-awareness-training-and-phishing"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T15:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Old-school awareness training does not hack it anymore. Your email filters have an average 7-10% failure rate; you need a strong human firewall as your last line of defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Discover Nearly 3,200 Mobile Apps Leaking Twitter API Keys]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-767016245283976229</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/researchers-discover-nearly-3200-mobile.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T14:09:45.936Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have uncovered a list of 3,207 apps, some of which can be utilized to gain unauthorized access to Twitter accounts.
The takeover is made possible, thanks to a leak of legitimate Consumer Key and Consumer Secret information, respectively, Singapore-based cybersecurity firm CloudSEK said in a report exclusively shared with The Hacker News.
"Out of 3,207, 230 apps are leaking all four]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Key Ways Development Teams Can Increase Their Security Maturity]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-7716716100793511137</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/08/two-key-ways-development-teams-can.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T14:05:14.046Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now more than ever, organizations need to enable their development teams to build and grow their security skills. Today organizations face a threat landscape where individuals, well-financed syndicates, and state actors are actively trying to exploit errors in software. Yet, according to recent global research, 67% of developers that were interviewed said they were still shipping code they knew]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Big Tech, Neutrality Is Not an Option — and Never Really Was]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/for-big-tech-neutrality-is-not-an-option-and-never-really-was</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/for-big-tech-neutrality-is-not-an-option-and-never-really-was"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech companies play a vital role in global communication, which has profound effects on how politics, policies, and human rights issues play out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francis Dinha, CEO &amp; Co-Founder, OpenVPN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Move to the Hybrid Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180335</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/secure-move-cloud/180335/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infosec expert Rani Osnat lays out security challenges and offers hope for organizations migrating their IT stack to the private and public cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Infosec Contributor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Widespread, Multistage Investment Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/a-widespread-multistage-investment-scam</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/a-widespread-multistage-investment-scam"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T12:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complex and ambitious investment scam has used more than 10,000 domains to induce speculators to give up not just funds, but personal information as well. Researchers at security firm Group-IB describe the campaign as one that proceeds through several distinct stages. It begins with ads placed in social media, or with pages displayed in compromised Facebook or YouTube accounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Hacker Charged with Creating, Selling Spyware to Cyber Criminals]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-2206789217564065274</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/australian-hacker-charged-with-creating.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T06:31:03.139Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 24-year-old Australian national has been charged for his purported role in the creation and sale of spyware for use by domestic violence perpetrators and child sex offenders.
Jacob Wayne John Keen, who currently resides at Frankston, Melbourne, is said to have created the remote access trojan (RAT) when he was 15, in addition to working as the administrator for the tool from 2013 until its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gootkit Loader Resurfaces with Updated Tactic to Compromise Targeted Computers]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3835892266038628283</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/gootkit-loader-resurfaces-with-updated.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T04:51:16.445Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The operators of the Gootkit access-as-a-service (AaaS) malware have resurfaced with updated techniques to compromise unsuspecting victims.
"In the past, Gootkit used freeware installers to mask malicious files; now it uses legal documents to trick users into downloading these files," Trend Micro researchers Buddy Tancio and Jed Valderama said in a write-up last week.

The findings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Putting Your Accounts At Risk, and Start Using a Password Manager]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-6003660466505173327</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/stop-putting-your-accounts-at-risk-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-30T17:20:07.093Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image via Keeper
Right Now, Get 30% Off Keeper, the Most Trusted Name in Password Management.
In one way or another, almost every aspect of our lives is online, so it’s no surprise that hackers target everything from email accounts to banks to smart home devices, looking for vulnerabilities to exploit. One of the easiest exploits is cracking a weak password. That’s why using a strong, unique]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Links Raspberry Robin USB Worm to Russian Evil Corp Hackers]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3522857160069435752</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/microsoft-links-raspberry-robin-usb.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-30T09:53:43.741Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Friday disclosed a potential connection between the Raspberry Robin USB-based worm and an infamous Russian cybercrime group tracked as Evil Corp.
The tech giant said it observed the FakeUpdates (aka SocGholish) malware being delivered via existing Raspberry Robin infections on July 26, 2022.
Raspberry Robin, also called QNAP Worm, is known to spread from a compromised system via]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Using Malicious Browser Extension to Spy on Email Accounts]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-356107816827825018</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/north-korean-hackers-using-malicious.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-30T04:20:43.972Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor operating with interests aligned with North Korea has been deploying a malicious extension on Chromium-based web browsers that's capable of stealing email content from Gmail and AOL.
Cybersecurity firm Volexity attributed the malware to an activity cluster it calls SharpTongue, which is said to share overlaps with an adversarial collective publicly referred to under the name]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Atlassian Confluence Hard-Coded Credential Bug Exploited in Attacks]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1657079912804334292</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/cisa-warns-of-atlassian-confluence-hard.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-30T04:01:25.120Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Friday added the recently disclosed Atlassian security flaw to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2022-26138, concerns the use of hard-coded credentials when the Questions For Confluence app is enabled in Confluence Server and Data Center]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Focuses on Identity Access Management at re:Inforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/aws-focuses-on-identity-access-management-at-re-inforce</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/aws-focuses-on-identity-access-management-at-re-inforce"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T20:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity and access management was front and center at AWS re:inforce this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Schwartz, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers Have 'Favorite' Vulnerabilities to Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-threat-monitor/attackers-have-favorite-vulnerabilities-to-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-threat-monitor/attackers-have-favorite-vulnerabilities-to-exploit"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T20:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While attackers continue to rely on older, unpatched vulnerabilities, many are jumping on new vulnerabilities as soon as they are disclosed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edge Editors, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICYMI: Dark Web Happenings Edition With Evil Corp., MSP Targeting & More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/icymi-dark-web-happenings-edition-evil-corp-msp-targeting</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/icymi-dark-web-happenings-edition-evil-corp-msp-targeting"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T19:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Reading's digest of other "don't-miss" stories of the week — including a Microsoft alert connecting disparate cybercrime activity together, and an explosion of Luca Stealer variants after an unusual Dark Web move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bug-Bounty Programs Are Failing Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/black-hat/why-bug-bounty-programs-failing-everyone</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/black-hat/why-bug-bounty-programs-failing-everyone"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T18:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Black Hat USA talk, Katie Moussouris will discuss why bug-bounty programs are failing in their goals, and what needs to happen next to use bounties in a way that improves security outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ericka Chickowski, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Teams Overwhelmed With Bugs, Bitten by Patch Prioritization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/security-teams-overwhelmed-bugs-patch-prioritization</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/security-teams-overwhelmed-bugs-patch-prioritization"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T16:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first half of the year saw more than 11,800 reported security vulnerabilities, but figuring out which ones to patch first remains a thankless job for IT teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Adds Malware Detection to GuardDuty TDR Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/amazon-adds-malware-detection-to-guardduty-tdr-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/amazon-adds-malware-detection-to-guardduty-tdr-service"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GuardDuty Malware Protection and Amazon Detective were among 10 products and services unveiled at AWS re:Inforce in Boston this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Schwartz, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>17837 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/29/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T15:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 29, 2022
CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation. These types of vulnerabilities are a frequent attack vector for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risk to the federal enterprise. Note: To view the newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column, which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known CVEs that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires FCEB agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the Catalog that meet the specified criteria.
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Questions Remain Around Massive Shanghai Police Data Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/questions-massive-shanghai-police-data-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/questions-massive-shanghai-police-data-breach"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T15:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why was PII belonging to nearly 1 billion people housed in a single, open database? Why didn't anyone notice it was downloaded?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Npm Packages Tapped Again to Target Discord Users]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180327</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/malicious-npm-discord/180327/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T15:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent LofyLife campaign steals tokens and infects client files to monitor various user actions, such as log-ins, password changes and payment methods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious npm Packages Scarf Up Discord Tokens, Credit Card Info]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/malicious-npm-packages-discord-tokens-credit-card</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/malicious-npm-packages-discord-tokens-credit-card"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T14:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The campaign uses four malicious packages to spread "Volt Stealer" and "Lofy Stealer" malware in the open source npm software package repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Tips for Creating a Security Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/3-tips-for-overcoming-challenges-to-creating-a-security-culture</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/3-tips-for-overcoming-challenges-to-creating-a-security-culture"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to get the whole organization on board with better cybersecurity is much tougher than it may sound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Lambert, Vice President of Product, Armorcode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over a Dozen Android Apps on Google Play Store Caught Dropping Banking Malware]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3636237590014702315</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/over-dozen-android-apps-on-google-play.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T13:25:15.764Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malicious campaign leveraged seemingly innocuous Android dropper apps on the Google Play Store to compromise users' devices with banking malware.
These 17 dropper apps, collectively dubbed DawDropper by Trend Micro, masqueraded as productivity and utility apps such as document scanners, QR code readers, VPN services, and call recorders, among others. All these apps in question have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Warns of Increase in Phishing Attacks Using Decentralized IPFS Network]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-8381520124406938203</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/researchers-warns-of-increase-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T13:07:02.742Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized file system solution known as IPFS is becoming the new "hotbed" for hosting phishing sites, researchers have warned.
Cybersecurity firm Trustwave SpiderLabs, which disclosed specifics of the attack campaigns, said it identified no less than 3,000 emails containing IPFS phishing URLs as an attack vector in the last three months.
IPFS, short for InterPlanetary File System, is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 23rd Annual SysAdmin Day from KnowBe4!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/happy-23rd-annual-sysadmin-day-from-knowbe4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/happy-23rd-annual-sysadmin-day-from-knowbe4"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been 23 years of celebrating all of our fellow System Administrators! Your hard work on daily maintenance of your company's day-to-day computer operations definitely deserves kudos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Combat the Biggest Security Risks Posed by Machine Identities]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-2115706251070278906</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/how-to-combat-biggest-security-risks_29.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T11:15:17.944Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of DevOps culture in enterprises has accelerated product delivery timelines. Automation undoubtedly has its advantages. However, containerization and the rise of cloud software development are exposing organizations to a sprawling new attack surface.
Machine identities vastly outnumber human ones in enterprises these days. Indeed, the rise of machine identities is creating cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your KnowBe4 Fresh Content Updates from July 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/your-knowbe4-fresh-content-updates-from-july-2022</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/your-knowbe4-fresh-content-updates-from-july-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the thirteen new pieces of training content added in July, alongside the always fresh content update highlights and new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dahua IP Camera Vulnerability Could Let Attackers Take Full Control Over Devices]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3399076208071864595</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/dahua-ip-camera-vulnerability-could-let.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T10:49:50.744Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have been shared about a security vulnerability in Dahua's Open Network Video Interface Forum (ONVIF) standard implementation, which, when exploited, can lead to seizing control of IP cameras. 
Tracked as CVE-2022-30563 (CVSS score: 7.4), the "vulnerability could be abused by attackers to compromise network cameras by sniffing a previous unencrypted ONVIF interaction and replaying the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish Police Arrest 2 Nuclear Power Workers for Cyberattacking the Radiation Alert System]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-5876230604234678851</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/spanish-police-arrest-2-nuclear-power.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T07:00:11.482Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish law enforcement officials have announced the arrest of two individuals in connection with a cyberattack on the country's radioactivity alert network (RAR), which took place between March and June 2021.
The act of sabotage is said to have disabled more than one-third of the sensors that are maintained by the Directorate-General for Civil Protection and Emergencies (DGPCE) and used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Opting New Attack Methods After Microsoft Blocked Macros by Default]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1445587106711714329</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/hackers-opting-new-attack-methods-after.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T06:08:24.637Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Microsoft taking steps to block Excel 4.0 (XLM or XL4) and Visual Basic for Applications (VBA) macros by default across Office apps, malicious actors are responding by refining their tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs).
"The use of VBA and XL4 Macros decreased approximately 66% from October 2021 through June 2022," Proofpoint said in a report shared with The Hacker News, calling it "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Critical Atlassian Confluence Vulnerability Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-7352621783823104679</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/latest-critical-atlassian-confluence.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T03:22:24.352Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week after Atlassian rolled out patches to contain a critical flaw in its Questions For Confluence app for Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center, the shortcoming has now come under active exploitation in the wild.
The bug in question is CVE-2022-26138, which concerns the use of a hard-coded password in the app that could be exploited by a remote, unauthenticated attacker to gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Offers $10 Million Reward for Information on North Korean Hackers]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-261514691794907768</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/us-offers-10-million-reward-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T02:58:42.556Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. State Department has announced rewards of up to $10 million for any information that could help disrupt North Korea's cryptocurrency theft, cyber-espionage, and other illicit state-backed activities.
"If you have information on any individuals associated with the North Korean government-linked malicious cyber groups (such as Andariel, APT38, Bluenoroff, Guardians of Peace, Kimsuky, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Uncovers Austrian Company Exploiting Windows and Adobe Zero-Day Exploits]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-5540475690254786785</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/microsoft-uncover-austrian-company.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T02:58:07.644Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cyber mercenary that "ostensibly sells general security and information analysis services to commercial customers" used several Windows and Adobe zero-day exploits in limited and highly-targeted attacks against European and Central American entities.
The company, which Microsoft describes as a private-sector offensive actor (PSOA), is an Austria-based outfit called DSIRF that's linked to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patch Now: Atlassian Confluence Bug Under Active Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/patch-now-atlassian-confluence-bug-active-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/patch-now-atlassian-confluence-bug-active-exploit"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers almost immediately leapt on a just-disclosed bug, CVE-2022-26138, affecting Atlassian Confluence, which allows remote, unauthenticated actors unfettered access to Confluence data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Actors Pivot Around Microsoft’s Macro-Blocking in Office]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180319</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/threat-pivot-microsofts-macro/180319/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T17:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals turn to container files and other tactics to get around the company’s attempt to thwart a popular way to deliver malicious phishing payloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the White House's Cybersecurity Workforce Plan Should Look Like]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/what-the-white-house-s-cybersecurity-workforce-plan-should-look-like</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/what-the-white-house-s-cybersecurity-workforce-plan-should-look-like"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By embracing cybersecurity as a critical part of our national security and education strategy, and working together to invest in opportunities for all, we can create a safer, more secure world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Schneider, CEO and President, Arctic Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of a Cloud-Service Security Update]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/?p=14470</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/2022/07/28/anatomy-of-a-cloud-service-security-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our security teams around the world focus on identifying and mitigating security issues as soon as possible while minimizing customer disruption. One of the challenges of a traditional security update is ensuring customers apply the protections promptly. We recently discussed the work that goes into these updates in The Anatomy of a Security update.  Cloud …
  Anatomy of a Cloud-Service Security Update Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aanchal Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT-Like Phishing Threat Mirrors Landing Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/apt-phishing-mirrors-landing-pages-credential-harvesting</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/apt-phishing-mirrors-landing-pages-credential-harvesting"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By dynamically mirroring an organization’s login page, threat actors are propagating legitimate-looking phishing attacks that encourage victims to offer up access to the corporate crown jewels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing-Based Data Breaches Take 295 Days to Contain and Breach Costs Soar to $4.91 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/phishing-based-data-breaches-take-295-days-to-contain-as-data-breaches-soar-to-4.91-million</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/phishing-based-data-breaches-take-295-days-to-contain-as-data-breaches-soar-to-4.91-million"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh data on data breach costs from IBM show phishing, business email compromise, and stolen credentials take the longest to identify and contain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Sophisticated Malicious USB Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/beware-of-sophisticated-malicious-usb-keys</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/beware-of-sophisticated-malicious-usb-keys"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious USB keys have always been a problem. There is almost no professional penetration testing team that does not drop a handful of USB keys outside of any targeted organization and see success from employees plugging them in and opening boobytrapped documents or running malicious executables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Grimes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Delays Blocking 3rd-Party Cookies in Chrome Browser Until 2024]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3627496762699990117</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/google-delays-blocking-3rd-party.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:16:39.681Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Wednesday said it's once again delaying its plans to turn off third-party cookies in the Chrome web browser from late 2023 to the second half of 2024.
"The most consistent feedback we've received is the need for more time to evaluate and test the new Privacy Sandbox technologies before deprecating third-party cookies in Chrome," Anthony Chavez, vice president of Privacy Sandbox, said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Log4Shell-Related MAR]]></title>
        <id>17836 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/28/cisa-releases-log4shell-related-mar-0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T14:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 28, 2022
From May through June 2022, CISA responded to an organization that was compromised by an exploitation of an unpatched and unmitigated Log4Shell vulnerability in a VMware Horizon server. CISA analyzed five malware samples obtained from the organization’s network and released a Malware Analysis Report of the findings.
Users and administrators are encouraged to review MAR 10386789-1.v1 for more information. For more information on Log4Shell, see:
Joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) Malicious Cyber Actors Continue to Exploit Log4Shell in VMware Horizon Systems,
CISA’s Apache Log4j Vulnerability Guidance webpage,
Joint CSA Mitigating Log4Shell and Other Log4j-Related Vulnerabilities, and
CISA’s database of known vulnerable services on the CISA GitHub page.
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Women Should Know Before Joining the Cybersecurity Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/what-women-should-know-before-joining-the-cybersecurity-industry</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/what-women-should-know-before-joining-the-cybersecurity-industry"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three observations about our industry that might help demystify security for women entrants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karin Ophir Zimet, VP, People &amp; Ops, Torq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Users are Once Again the Target of Phishing Scams using Fake Voice Mail Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/microsoft-365-users-are-once-again-the-target-of-phishing-scams-using-fake-voice-mail-messages</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/microsoft-365-users-are-once-again-the-target-of-phishing-scams-using-fake-voice-mail-messages"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a simple email containing a voice mail attachment, an ingenious phishing attack captures credentials while keeping track of the domains being attacked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Use Free Email Accounts from QuickBooks to Launch Spoofed Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/hackers-use-free-email-accounts-from-quickbooks-to-launch-spoofed-phishing-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/hackers-use-free-email-accounts-from-quickbooks-to-launch-spoofed-phishing-attacks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new attack uses one brand email domain to increase the chances of reaching an Inbox, while spoofing another brand to trick users into transitioning to a vishing attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spear Phishing Campaign Targets Facebook Business Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/spear-phishing-campaign-targets-facebook-business-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/spear-phishing-campaign-targets-facebook-business-accounts"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers at WithSecure have discovered a spear phishing campaign targeting employees who have access to Facebook Business accounts. The attackers are targeting specific employees, and then sending malware through LinkedIn messages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1,000s of Phishing Attacks Blast Off From InterPlanetary File System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/1000s-phishing-attacks-launch-interplanetary-file-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/1000s-phishing-attacks-launch-interplanetary-file-system"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The peer-to-peer network IPFS offers an ingenious base for cyberattacks and is seeing a stratospheric increase in malicious hosting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM: Phishing is the Most Common Way to Gain Access to Victim Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/ibm-phishing-is-the-most-common-way-to-gain-access-to-victim-networks</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/ibm-phishing-is-the-most-common-way-to-gain-access-to-victim-networks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T12:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research from IBM shows four reasons why phishing attacks are still effective and remains the primary attack vector in 41% of cyberattacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top MSSP CEOs Share 7 Must-Do Tips for Higher MSSP Revenue and Margin]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-7694134648739077799</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/top-mssp-ceos-share-7-must-do-tips-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:11:03.297Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSSPs must find ways to balance the need to please existing customers, add new ones, and deliver high-margin services against their internal budget constraints and the need to maintain high employee morale.In an environment where there are thousands of potential alerts each day and cyberattacks are growing rapidly in frequency and sophistication, this isn’t an easy balance to maintain.
Customers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ducktail Infostealer Malware Targeting Facebook Business and Ad Accounts]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1234838757475555764</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/new-ducktail-infostealer-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T10:56:39.887Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook business and advertising accounts are at the receiving end of an ongoing campaign dubbed Ducktail designed to seize control as part of a financially driven cybercriminal operation. 
"The threat actor targets individuals and employees that may have access to a Facebook Business account with an information-stealer malware," Finnish cybersecurity company WithSecure (formerly F-Secure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In a Post-Macro World, Container Files Emerge as Malware-Delivery Replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/post-macro-world-container-files-distribute-malware-replacement</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/post-macro-world-container-files-distribute-malware-replacement"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Microsoft disabling Office macros by default, threat actors are increasingly using ISO, RAR, LNK, and similar files to deliver malware because they can get around Windows protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreOffice Releases Software Update to Patch 3 New Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1211581427129802840</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/libreoffice-releases-software-security.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T06:42:06.885Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team behind LibreOffice has released security updates to fix three security flaws in the productivity software, one of which could be exploited to achieve arbitrary code execution on affected systems.
Tracked as CVE-2022-26305, the issue has been described as a case of improper certificate validation when checking whether a macro is signed by a trusted author, leading to the execution of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Human Security Meets PerimeterX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/when-human-security-meets-perimeterx</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/when-human-security-meets-perimeterx"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T00:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Reading's analysis suggests that the merger between Human Security and PerimeterX will bring modern defense strategies to disrupt cybercrime and fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Care, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneTouchPoint, Inc. Provides Notice of Data Privacy Event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/onetouchpoint-inc-provides-notice-of-data-privacy-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/onetouchpoint-inc-provides-notice-of-data-privacy-event"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T23:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming the Fail-to-Challenge Vulnerability With a Friendly Face]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/overcoming-the-fail-to-challenge-vulnerability-with-a-friendly-face</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/overcoming-the-fail-to-challenge-vulnerability-with-a-friendly-face"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T23:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of their Black Hat USA talk in August, Simon Pavitt and Stephen Dewsnip explain the value of helping people practice cyber defense via a "malicious floorwalker" exercise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Spiegelman, Features Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samba Releases Security Updates]]></title>
        <id>17833 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/27/samba-releases-security-updates"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T20:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 27, 2022 | Last revised: July 28, 2022
The Samba Team has released security updates to address vulnerabilities in multiple versions of Samba. An attacker could exploit one of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system. 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following Samba Security Announcements and apply the necessary updates and workarounds. 
•    CVE-2022-2031  
CVE-2022-32742
CVE-2022-32744
CVE-2022-32745
CVE-2022-32746

 
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Windows, Adobe Zero-Days Anchor Knotweed Commercial Spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/windows-adobe-zero-days-knotweed-commercial-spyware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/windows-adobe-zero-days-knotweed-commercial-spyware"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T18:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft flagged the company's Subzero tool set as on offer to unscrupulous governments and shady business interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Offers $10M Double-Reward for North Korea Cyberattacker Info]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/us-10m-double-reward-north-korea-cyberattacker-info</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/us-10m-double-reward-north-korea-cyberattacker-info"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean state-sponsored actors, who help economically prop up Kim Jong Un's dictatorship, continue to pummel US infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Average Data Breach Costs Soar to $4.4M in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/most-companies-pass-on-breach-costs-to-customers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/most-companies-pass-on-breach-costs-to-customers"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call it a "cyber tax": Those costs are usually passed on to consumers, not investors, as compromised businesses raise prices for goods and services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Your Home or Small Business Built on Secure Foundations? Think Again…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/physical-security/is-your-home-or-small-business-built-on-secure-foundations-think-again-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/physical-security/is-your-home-or-small-business-built-on-secure-foundations-think-again-"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that the standard router relied upon in homes and by thousands of small businesses is the most frequently attacked IoT device? James Willison, Project and Engagement Manager, IoT Security Foundation, explores the issue and reveals an ongoing initiative from the foundation that is designed to better secure the devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IFSEC Global, Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Spotlight: How a code re-use issue led to vulnerabilities across multiple products]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/vulnerability-spotlight-how-code-re-use.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/vulnerability-spotlight-how-code-re-use.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Francesco Benvenuto. 
Recently, I was performing some research on a wireless router and noticed the following piece of code: 

This unescape function will revert the URL encoded bytes to its original form. But something specifically caught my attention: There was no size check for the performed operations and the function assumes that after a ‘%’ there are always two bytes. So, what would happen if after ‘%’, only one character existed? The answer is that the s+3, in the strcpy, will access after the end of the string. So, it could lead to memory corruption. 
Then, I tried to exploit this bug on the router in question. But based on how the URL string was managed in that device, it was not possible. But it had the potential to crash other web servers that used this piece of code. That fu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cisco Talos Intelligence Group - Comprehensive Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KnowBe4 Top-Clicked Phishing Email Subjects for Q2 2022 [INFOGRAPHIC]]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/top-clicked-phishing-emails-q2-2022-infographic</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/top-clicked-phishing-emails-q2-2022-infographic"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KnowBe4's latest quarterly report on top-clicked phishing email subjects is here. We analyze 'in the wild' attacks reported via our Phish Alert Button, top subjects globally clicked on in phishing tests, and top attack vector types.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Cohort Graduates from PSM Cyber Stars Program at Liverpool FC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/first-cohort-graduates-from-psm-cyber-stars-program-at-liverpool-fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/first-cohort-graduates-from-psm-cyber-stars-program-at-liverpool-fc"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New careers in IT open up for former footballers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great BizApp Hack: Cyber-Risks in Your Everyday Business Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/the-great-bizapp-hack-cyber-risks-in-your-everyday-business-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/the-great-bizapp-hack-cyber-risks-in-your-everyday-business-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT admins can lock some of the obvious open doors in business applications, but system visibility is key. Build automatic monitoring defenses and adopt a Git-like tool so you can "version" your business apps to restore prior states.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gil Hoffer, Co-Founder and Chief Technology Officer, Salto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No More Ransom Helped More Than 1.5 Million People Decrypt Their Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/no-more-ransom-helped-more-than-1-5-million-people-decrypt-their-devices</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/no-more-ransom-helped-more-than-1-5-million-people-decrypt-their-devices"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T13:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 28+ Android Apps with 10 Million Downloads from the Play Store Contain Malware]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-5900010080829563595</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/these-28-android-apps-with-10-million.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T13:37:25.653Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 30 malicious Android apps with cumulative downloads of nearly 10 million have been found on the Google Play Store distributing adware.
"All of them were built into various programs, including image-editing software, virtual keyboards, system tools and utilities, calling apps, wallpaper collection apps, and others," Dr.Web said in a Tuesday write-up.
While masquerading as innocuous]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Hot Summer Fiction Reads for Cybersecurity Pros]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/8-hot-summer-fiction-reads-for-cybersecurity-pros-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/8-hot-summer-fiction-reads-for-cybersecurity-pros-"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reading list of recommended novels curated by cybersecurity experts for cybersecurity experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Zurier, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly Half of Organizations Have Experienced Vishing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/nearly-half-of-organizations-have-experienced-vishing</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/nearly-half-of-organizations-have-experienced-vishing"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forty-seven percent of organizations have experienced voice phishing (vishing) attacks over the past year, according to researchers at Mutare. Additionally, the researchers found that nine percent of all phone calls received by organizations are unwanted, and nearly half of these are malicious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Report Reveals that Ransomware and Business Email Compromise Attacks Cause Nearly 70% of Cyber Incidents]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/new-report-reveals-that-ransomware-and-business-email-compromise-attacks-cause-nearly-70-of-cyber-incidents</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/new-report-reveals-that-ransomware-and-business-email-compromise-attacks-cause-nearly-70-of-cyber-incidents"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know your organizations true security risk and where to prioritize your resources? A new report from Palo Alto Networks sheds some light on these questions and shows multiple insights on incident response work from security teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Steps the Financial Industry Can Take to Cope With Their Growing Attack Surface]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-8085108392141568266</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/4-steps-financial-industry-can-take-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:16:55.947Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financial services industry has always been at the forefront of technology adoption, but the 2020 pandemic accelerated the widespread of mobile banking apps, chat-based customer service, and other digital tools. Adobe's 2022 FIS Trends Report, for instance, found that more than half of the financial services and insurance firms surveyed experienced a notable increase in digital/mobile]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the Risk-Based Approach to Vulnerability Patching]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3535342024531027243</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/taking-risk-based-approach-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:00:30.996Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software vulnerabilities are a major threat to organizations today. The cost of these threats is significant, both financially and in terms of reputation.Vulnerability management and patching can easily get out of hand when the number of vulnerabilities in your organization is in the hundreds of thousands of vulnerabilities and tracked in inefficient ways, such as using Excel spreadsheets or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Increasingly Using WebAssembly Coded Cryptominers to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-3036964450138540237</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/hackers-increasingly-using-webassembly.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:57:05.537Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 207 websites have been infected with malicious code designed to launch a cryptocurrency miner by leveraging WebAssembly (Wasm) on the browser.
Web security company Sucuri, which published details of the campaign, said it launched an investigation after one of its clients had their computer slowed down significantly every time upon navigating to their own WordPress portal.
This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious IIS Extensions Gaining Popularity Among Cyber Criminals for Persistent Access]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1248449795096942156</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/malicious-iis-extensions-gaining.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:17:05.805Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are increasingly abusing Internet Information Services (IIS) extensions to backdoor servers as a means of establishing a "durable persistence mechanism."
That's according to a new warning from the Microsoft 365 Defender Research Team, which said that "IIS backdoors are also harder to detect since they mostly reside in the same directories as legitimate modules used by target]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SmokeLoader Infecting Targeted Systems with Amadey Info-Stealing Malware]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-4626974502942287752</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/smokeloader-infecting-targeted-systems.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T06:36:38.597Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An information-stealing malware called Amadey is being distributed by means of another backdoor called SmokeLoader.
The attacks hinge on tricking users into downloading SmokeLoader that masquerades as software cracks, paving the way for the deployment of Amadey, researchers from the AhnLab Security Emergency Response Center (ASEC) said in a report published last week.

Amadey, a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Newmark Gives UC Berkeley $2 Million for University Cybersecurity Clinics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/craig-newmark-gives-uc-berkeley-2-million-for-university-cybersecurity-clinics</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/craig-newmark-gives-uc-berkeley-2-million-for-university-cybersecurity-clinics"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T22:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norton Consumer Cyber Safety Pulse Report: Phishing for New Bait on Social Media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/norton-consumer-cyber-safety-pulse-report-phishing-for-new-bait-on-social-media</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/norton-consumer-cyber-safety-pulse-report-phishing-for-new-bait-on-social-media"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T22:23:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Year-long analysis from Norton Labs finds nearly three-quarters of phishing sites imitate Facebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit 3.0: Significantly Improved Ransomware Helps the Gang Stay on Top]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/lockbit-3.0-improved-malware-gang-top</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/lockbit-3.0-improved-malware-gang-top"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just ahead of its headline-grabbing attack on the Italian tax agency, the infamous ransomware group debuted an improved version of the malware featuring parts from Egregor and BlackMatter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Tops Brands Phishers Prefer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/microsoft-tops-brands-phishers-prefer</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/microsoft-tops-brands-phishers-prefer"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T20:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wide use of Microsoft 365 applications by business lets phishers easily launch data theft, BEC, ransomware, and other attacks, new report finds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economic Downturn Raises Risk of Insiders Going Rogue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/economic-downturn-raises-the-risk-of-insiders-going-rogue</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/economic-downturn-raises-the-risk-of-insiders-going-rogue"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insiders could become more vulnerable to cybercrime recruitment efforts, new report says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Can Help Fintechs Fight Fraud-as-a-Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/ai-can-help-fintechs-fight-fraud-as-a-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/ai-can-help-fintechs-fight-fraud-as-a-service"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T20:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence tools can help companies strike the right balance between preventing financial crime and maintaining customer service and satisfaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Brodhurst, Principal Consultant, Resistant AI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord, Telegram Services Hijacked to Launch Array of Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/discord-telegram-hijacked-cyberattacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/discord-telegram-hijacked-cyberattacks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are easily turning popular messaging apps and their associated services — like bots, cloud infrastructure, and CDNs — against users, researchers warn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flying Blind in Security Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/flying-blind-in-security-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/flying-blind-in-security-operations"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T17:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too many organizations are STILL getting breached. Every day across large and small organizations, intrusions and breaches happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Risk-Based Vulnerability Management Has Made Security Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/how-risk-based-vulnerability-management-has-made-security-easier</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/how-risk-based-vulnerability-management-has-made-security-easier"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to remediate everything was never a winning strategy. RBVM is an approach that gets organizations better results with less effort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Bellis, Co-Founder and CTO, Kenna Security, now a part of Cisco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ducktail Spear-Phishing Campaign Uses LinkedIn to Hijack Facebook Business Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/ducktail-spearphishing-linkedin-hijack-facebook-business-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/ducktail-spearphishing-linkedin-hijack-facebook-business-accounts"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ducktail targets marketing and HR professionals through LinkedIn to hijack Facebook accounts and run malvertising schemes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Find Similarities Between New LockBit 3.0 and BlackMatter Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-9124630298261290725</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/experts-find-similarities-between.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:16:45.040Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have reiterated similarities between the latest iteration of the LockBit ransomware and BlackMatter, a rebranded variant of the DarkSide ransomware strain that closed shop in November 2021.
The new version of LockBit, called LockBit 3.0 aka LockBit Black, was released in June 2022, launching a brand new leak site and what's the very first ransomware bug bounty program,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[BEWARE] Microsoft and Facebook are the Most Abused Brands for Phishing Attempts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.knowbe4.com/beware-microsoft-and-facebook-are-the-most-abused-brands-for-phishing-attempts</id>
        <link href="https://blog.knowbe4.com/beware-microsoft-and-facebook-are-the-most-abused-brands-for-phishing-attempts"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T15:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know that big brands can be exploited by bad actors in order to execute successful phishing attacks. Now a new study is showing phishing attacks leveraging big brands Microsoft and Facebook as the top abused brands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stu Sjouwerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beautiful Lies of Machine Learning in Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/the-beautiful-lies-of-machine-learning-in-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/the-beautiful-lies-of-machine-learning-in-security"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning should be considered an extension of — not a replacement for — existing security methods, systems, and teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Belak, Director of Thought Leadership, Sysdig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siemens Energy Takes Next Step to Protect Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/siemens-energy-takes-next-step-to-protect-critical-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/siemens-energy-takes-next-step-to-protect-critical-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T13:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company joins AWS Partner Network to provide customers with industrial cybersecurity solution to ensure reliable electricity and fuel supplies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT Botnets Fuels DDoS Attacks – Are You Prepared?]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180273</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/ddos-attacks-prepared/180273/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T12:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increased proliferation of IoT devices paved the way for the rise of IoT botnets that amplifies DDoS attacks today. This is a dangerous warning that the possibility of a sophisticated DDoS attack and a prolonged service outage will prevent businesses from growing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT Botnets Fuels DDoS Attacks – Are You Prepared?]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180273</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/ddos-attacks-prepared/180273/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T12:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increased proliferation of IoT devices paved the way for the rise of IoT botnets that amplifies DDoS attacks today. This is a dangerous warning that the possibility of a sophisticated DDoS attack and a prolonged service outage will prevent businesses from growing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Adds Default Protection Against RDP Brute-Force Attacks in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-550039964870809907</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/microsoft-adds-default-protection.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:50:27.718Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is now taking steps to prevent Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) brute-force attacks as part of the latest builds for the Windows 11 operating system in an attempt to raise the security baseline to meet the evolving threat landscape.
To that end, the default policy for Windows 11 builds – particularly, Insider Preview builds 22528.1000 and newer – will automatically lock accounts for 10]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit PrestaShop Zero-Day to Steal Payment Data from Online Stores]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-2582996623465099477</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/hackers-exploit-prestashop-zero-day-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:50:06.277Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors are exploiting a previously unknown security flaw in the open source PrestaShop e-commerce platform to inject malicious skimmer code designed to swipe sensitive information.
"Attackers have found a way to use a security vulnerability to carry out arbitrary code execution in servers running PrestaShop websites," the company noted in an advisory published on July 22.
PrestaShop is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical FileWave MDM Flaws Open Organization-Managed Devices to Remote Hackers]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-6147719882988217900</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/critical-filewave-mdm-flaws-open.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T10:12:33.871Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FileWave's mobile device management (MDM) system has been found vulnerable to two critical security flaws that could be leveraged to carry out remote attacks and seize control of a fleet of devices connected to it.
"The vulnerabilities are remotely exploitable and enable an attacker to bypass authentication mechanisms and gain full control over the MDM platform and its managed devices," Claroty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover New 'CosmicStrand' UEFI Firmware Rootkit Used by Chinese Hackers]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-5372934004426975352</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/experts-uncover-new-cosmicstrand-uefi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T02:59:46.106Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown Chinese-speaking threat actor has been attributed to a new kind of sophisticated Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) firmware rootkit called CosmicStrand.
"The rootkit is located in the firmware images of Gigabyte or ASUS motherboards, and we noticed that all these images are related to designs using the H81 chipset," Kaspersky researchers said in a new report published today]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Mantis Financial Hackers Targeting Android and iPhone Users in France]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-8239508243729692194</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/roaming-mantis-financial-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T02:58:12.608Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mobile threat campaign tracked as Roaming Mantis has been linked to a new wave of compromises directed against French mobile phone users, months after it expanded its targeting to include European countries.
No fewer than 70,000 Android devices are said to have been infected as part of the active malware operation, Sekoia said in a report published last week.
Attack chains involving Roaming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenFHE Brings New Encryption Tools to Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/openfhe-brings-new-encryption-tools-to-developers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/openfhe-brings-new-encryption-tools-to-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T01:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open source fully homomorphic encryption library from Duality Technologies is intended to help developers build their own FHE-enabled applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare 'CosmicStrand' UEFI Rootkit Swings into Cybercrime Orbit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/rare-cosmicstrand-uefi-rootkit-cybercrime-orbit</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/rare-cosmicstrand-uefi-rootkit-cybercrime-orbit"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firmware threat offers ultimate stealth and persistence — and may be distributed via tainted firmware components in a supply chain play, researchers theorize.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharged Version of Amadey Infostealer & Malware Dropper Bypasses AVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/supercharged-version-amadey-infostealer-malware-dropper-bypass-av</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/supercharged-version-amadey-infostealer-malware-dropper-bypass-av"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several threat actors used Amadey Bot previously to steal information and distribute malware such as the GandCrab ransomware and the FlawedAmmy RAT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile Pitches $4-Per-Customer Settlement for Data Leak Impacting 80M People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/t-mobile-pitches-4-per-customer-settlement-for-data-leak</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/t-mobile-pitches-4-per-customer-settlement-for-data-leak"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After leaking 80 million US customer data records in a cyberattack last summer, T-Mobile offers to settle a wide-ranging class action suit for just $350 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Layer 8 Is Great]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/why-layer-8-is-great</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/why-layer-8-is-great"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help discern legitimate traffic from fraud, it helps to understand user intent as shown through their behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Goldfarb, Fraud Solutions Architect - EMEA and APCJ, F5</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qakbot Is Back With a New Trick: DLL Sideloading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/qakbot-back-new-trick-dll-sideloading</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/qakbot-back-new-trick-dll-sideloading"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest iteration, Qakbot operators are using DLL sideloading to deliver malware, a technique that places legitimate and malicious files together in a common directory to avoid detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aqua Launches Out-of-the-Box Runtime Security with Advanced Protection against the Most Sophisticated Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/aqua-launches-out-of-the-box-runtime-security-with-advanced-protection-against-the-most-sophisticated-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/aqua-launches-out-of-the-box-runtime-security-with-advanced-protection-against-the-most-sophisticated-threats"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security professionals can now achieve real-time protection for their workloads in minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/getting-ahead-of-supply-chain-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/getting-ahead-of-supply-chain-attacks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are willing to replicate entire networks, purchase domains, and persist for months, not to mention spend significantly to make these campaigns successful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Mullins, CTO, Deepwatch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Filewave MDM Vulnerabilities Allow Attackers Full Mobile Device Control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-filewave-mdm-vulnerabilities-attackers-mobile-device-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-filewave-mdm-vulnerabilities-attackers-mobile-device-control"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two previously unknown critical vulnerabilities within FileWave’s multiplatform MDM system could grant malicious actors access to the platform's most privileged user account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magecart Hacks Food Ordering Systems to Steal Payment Data from Over 300 Restaurants]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-9041981165604755055</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/magecart-hacks-online-food-ordering.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:13:38.317Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three restaurant ordering platforms MenuDrive, Harbortouch, and InTouchPOS were the target of two Magecart skimming campaigns that resulted in the compromise of at least 311 restaurants.
The trio of breaches has led to the theft of more than 50,000 payment card records from these infected restaurants and posted for sale on the dark web.
"The online ordering platforms MenuDrive and Harbortouch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racoon Stealer is Back — How to Protect Your Organization]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-1034877945616757810</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/racoon-stealer-is-back-how-to-protect.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T08:52:13.242Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Racoon Stealer malware as a service platform gained notoriety several years ago for its ability to extract data that is stored within a Web browser. This data initially included passwords and cookies, which sometimes allow a recognized device to be authenticated without a password being entered. Racoon Stealer was also designed to steal auto-fill data, which can include a vast trove of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Proposed SEC Rules Through an ESG Lens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/understanding-proposed-sec-rules-through-an-environmental-social-and-governance-lens</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/understanding-proposed-sec-rules-through-an-environmental-social-and-governance-lens"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T22:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber threats are putting environmental, social, and governance discussions at the forefront of board meetings and C-suite discussions around the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Lawton, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICYMI: Neopets & the Gaming Problem; SolarWinds Hackers Are Back; Google Ads Abused]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/icymi-neopets-gaming-google-ads-abused-solarwinds-hackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/icymi-neopets-gaming-google-ads-abused-solarwinds-hackers"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T21:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Reading's weekly roundup of all the OTHER important stories of the week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Bugs Threaten to Crack Atlassian Confluence Workspaces Wide Open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-bugs-atlassian-confluence-workspaces-open</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-bugs-atlassian-confluence-workspaces-open"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T19:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hardcoded password associated with the Questions for Confluence app has been publicly released, which will likely lead to exploit attempts that give cyberattackers access to all Confluence content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall Issues Patch for Critical Bug Affecting its Analytics and GMS Products]]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-2297642232426241877</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/sonicwall-issues-patch-for-critical-bug.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:39:32.193Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network security company SonicWall on Friday rolled out fixes to mitigate a critical SQL injection (SQLi) vulnerability affecting its Analytics On-Prem and Global Management System (GMS) products.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2022-22280, is rated 9.4 for severity on the CVSS scoring system and stems from what the company describes is an "improper neutralization of special elements" used in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Resumes Blocking Office VBA Macros by Default After 'Temporary Pause']]></title>
        <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4802841478634147276.post-2891165774815019434</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2022/07/microsoft-resumes-blocking-office-vba.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:27:30.282Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has officially resumed blocking Visual Basic for Applications (VBA) macros by default across Office apps, weeks after temporarily announcing plans to roll back the change.
"Based on our review of customer feedback, we've made updates to both our end user and our IT admin documentation to make clearer what options you have for different scenarios," the company said in an update on July]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noreply@blogger.com (Ravie Lakshmanan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Zero-Day Weaponized to Spy on Journalists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/google-chrome-0-day-weaponized-to-spy-on-journalists</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/google-chrome-0-day-weaponized-to-spy-on-journalists"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Candiru attackers breached a news agency employee website to target journalists with DevilsTongue spyware, researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snowballing Ransomware Variants Highlight Growing Threat to VMware ESXi Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/snowballing-ransomware-variants-highlight-growing-threat-to-vmware-esxi-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/snowballing-ransomware-variants-highlight-growing-threat-to-vmware-esxi-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T16:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luna, Black Basta add to rapidly growing list of malware tools targeted at virtual machines deployed on VMware's bare-metal hypervisor technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing Bonanza: Social-Engineering Savvy Skyrockets as Malicious Actors Cash In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/phishing-bonanza-social-engineering-skyrockets-malicious-actors-cash-in</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/phishing-bonanza-social-engineering-skyrockets-malicious-actors-cash-in"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-evolving threat from phishing is growing more sophisticated as attackers design high-pressure situations and leverage ever-more-convincing social engineering tactics to increase their success rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thales Expands Cybersecurity Portfolio With OneWelcome Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/omdia/thales-expands-cybersecurity-portfolio-with-onewelcome-acquisition</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/omdia/thales-expands-cybersecurity-portfolio-with-onewelcome-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more staff working remotely, identity, authentication, and access have never been more important.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Tait, Senior Analyst, Omdia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases Security Updates for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>17825 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/22/apple-releases-security-updates-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 22, 2022
Apple has released security updates to address vulnerabilities in multiple products. These updates address vulnerabilities attackers could exploit to take control of affected systems.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the Apple security updates and apply necessary releases.
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Releases Security Updates for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>17824 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/22/cisco-releases-security-updates-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 22, 2022
Cisco has released security updates to address vulnerabilities in multiple products. Some of these vulnerabilities could allow a remote attacker to execute take control of an affected system. For updates addressing lower severity vulnerabilities, see the Cisco Security Advisories page. 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the Cisco advisories and apply the necessary updates.
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Releases Security Advisory for Questions for Confluence App, CVE-2022-26138]]></title>
        <id>17823 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/22/atlassian-releases-security-advisory-questions-confluence-app-cve"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 22, 2022
Atlassian has released a security advisory to address a vulnerability (CVE-2022-26138) affecting Questions for Confluence App. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information. Atlassian reports that the vulnerability is likely to be exploited in the wild.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Atlassian’s security advisory, Questions For Confluence Security Advisory 2022-07-20, and apply the necessary updates immediately. 
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Firewalls Can — and Can't — Accomplish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/what-firewalls-can-and-can-t-accomplish</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/what-firewalls-can-and-can-t-accomplish"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the limitations of firewalls is important to protecting the organization from evolving threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pat McGarry, Chief Technology Officer, ThreatBlockr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious, Cloud-Enabled macOS Spyware Blows Onto the Scene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/mysterious-cloud-enabled-macos-spyware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/mysterious-cloud-enabled-macos-spyware"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T20:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CloudMensis spyware, which can lift reams of sensitive information from Apple machines, is the first Mac malware observed to exclusively rely on cloud storage for C2 activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Critical Patch Update Addresses 349 Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://fieldeffect.com/?post_type=threats&amp;p=6500</id>
        <link href="https://fieldeffect.com/threats/oracle-critical-patch-update-addresses-349-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 19 July 2022, Oracle issued a Critical Patch Update fixing 349 vulnerabilities; many of these can be used for remote execution of code without authentication. We recommend applying the latest updates as soon as possible. Details The Critical Patch Update (CPU) addresses vulnerabilities in multiple Oracle product families and their third-party components; 64 of these were […]
The post Oracle Critical Patch Update Addresses 349 Flaws appeared first on Field Effect Software Inc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Lapina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equitable Digital Identity Verification Requires Moving Past Flawed Legacy Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/equitable-digital-identity-verification-requires-moving-past-flawed-legacy-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/equitable-digital-identity-verification-requires-moving-past-flawed-legacy-systems"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data science can be used to improve access to government assistance while reducing fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Burris, Senior Director of Product Market Strategy for the Public Sector, Socure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Becomes First Cloud Operator to Join Healthcare ISAC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/google-cloud-join-healthcare-isac</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/google-cloud-join-healthcare-isac"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T17:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud pledges experts and other resources to Health Information Sharing and Analysis Center, a community of healthcare infrastructure operators and owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Releases Security Updates for Chrome]]></title>
        <id>17817 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/21/google-releases-security-updates-chrome"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 21, 2022
Google has released Chrome version 103.0.5060.134  for Windows, Mac, and Linux. This version addresses vulnerabilities that an attacker could exploit to take control of an affected system.  
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the Chrome Release Note and apply the necessary updates. 
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drupal Releases Security Update]]></title>
        <id>17816 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/21/drupal-releases-security-update"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 21, 2022
Drupal has released security updates to address vulnerabilities affecting Drupal 9.3 and 9.4. An attacker could exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.  
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Drupal security advisory SA-CORE-2022-015 and apply the necessary update.  
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNMF Discloses Malware in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>17815 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/21/cnmf-discloses-malware-ukraine"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 21, 2022
U.S. Cyber Command’s Cyber National Mission Force (CNMF), in close coordination with the Security Service of Ukraine, has released a list of indicators of compromise (IOCs) of malware seen in Ukraine. According to CNMF, “Ukrainian partners are actively sharing malicious activity they find with us to bolster collective cyber security, just as we are sharing with them.” 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review U.S. Cyber Command’s press release, Cyber National Mission Force discloses IOCs from Ukrainian networks, as well as their VirusTotal and GitHub pages for more information. See Mandiant’s report, Evacuation and Humanitarian Documents used to Spear Phish Ukrainian Entities, for additional information.  
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Market Is Teeming: Bargains on Dark Web Give Novice Cybercriminals a Quick Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/market-bargains-dark-web-novice-cybercriminals-quick-start</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/market-bargains-dark-web-novice-cybercriminals-quick-start"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study of the unregulated dark markets shows that the vast majority of malware, exploits, and attacker tools sell for less than $10, giving would-be criminals a fast entry point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kronos Ransomware Attack: What You Need to Know So Your Business Isn't Next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/the-kronos-ransomware-attack-what-you-need-to-know-so-your-business-isn-t-next</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/the-kronos-ransomware-attack-what-you-need-to-know-so-your-business-isn-t-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identify your business's security posture and head off ransomware attacks with third-party risk management and vendor security assessments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Wilkes, Chief Information Security Officer, SecurityScorecard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercrime Group TA4563 Targets DeFi Market With Evolving Evilnum Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/cybercrime-ta4563-defi-market-evilnum</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/cybercrime-ta4563-defi-market-evilnum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cyber campaign, aimed at siphoning funds, uses an improved version of the malware, which can adjust infection paths based on recognized antivirus software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Professionals Push Their Organizations Toward Vendor Consolidation and Product Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cybersecurity-professionals-push-their-organizations-toward-vendor-consolidation-and-product-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cybersecurity-professionals-push-their-organizations-toward-vendor-consolidation-and-product-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T22:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New global study from ESG and ISSA reveals nearly half of organizations are consolidating or plan on consolidating the number of vendors they do business with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lax Security Fuels Massive 8220 Gang Botnet Army Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/lax-security-fuels-cloud-botnet-army-surge</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/lax-security-fuels-cloud-botnet-army-surge"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat group 8220 Gang's cryptocurrency miner and botnet reach has exploded to 30,000 global hosts, a notable increase over the past month, researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['AIG' Threat Group Launches With Unique Business Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/aig-threat-group-launches-unique-business-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/aig-threat-group-launches-unique-business-model"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapidly growing Atlas Intelligence Group relies on cyber-mercenaries to carry out its missions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Releases July 2022 Critical Patch Update]]></title>
        <id>17812 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/20/oracle-releases-july-2022-critical-patch-update"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 20, 2022 | Last revised: July 21, 2022
Oracle has released its Critical Patch Update for July 2022 to address 349 vulnerabilities across multiple products. A remote attacker could exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.  
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the Oracle July 2022 Critical Patch Update and apply the necessary updates.  
 
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Recoup $500K From Maui Ransomware Gang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/feds-recoup-500k-maui-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/feds-recoup-500k-maui-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement hopes that retuning ransom payments to impacted businesses will demonstrate that working with the feds following a cybersecurity breach is "good business."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data-Centric Security Market Worth $12.3B by 2027 - Exclusive Report by MarketsandMarkets™]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/data-centric-security-market-worth-12-3b-by-2027---exclusive-report-by-marketsandmarkets-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/data-centric-security-market-worth-12-3b-by-2027---exclusive-report-by-marketsandmarkets-"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutare Voice Network Threat Survey Shows Nearly Half of Organizations Experienced Vishing or Social Engineering Attacks in Past Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/mutare-voice-network-threat-survey-shows-nearly-half-of-organizations-experienced-vishing-or-social-engineering-attacks-in-past-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/mutare-voice-network-threat-survey-shows-nearly-half-of-organizations-experienced-vishing-or-social-engineering-attacks-in-past-year"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsecured voice traffic, skyrocketing adoption of Teams-centric enterprise collaboration tools widen enterprise cybersecurity gaps and increase risk of breach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What InfoSec Pros Can Teach the Organization About ESG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/what-infosec-pros-can-teach-the-organization-about-esg</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/what-infosec-pros-can-teach-the-organization-about-esg"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security pros' experience with transparency and evaluating third-party partners positions them to act as key environmental, social, and governance advisers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Marcus, Head of Information Security, AuditBoard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chaotic LAPSUS$ Group Goes Quiet, but Threat Likely Persists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/chaotic-lapsus-quiet-threat-persists</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/chaotic-lapsus-quiet-threat-persists"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LAPSUS$ group emerged with a big splash at the end of 2021, targeting companies, including Okta, with a "reckless and disruptive" approach to hacking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Mitigate the Risk of Karakurt Data Extortion Group's Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/how-to-mitigate-the-risk-of-karakurt-data-extortion-group-s-tactics-techniques-and-procedures</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/how-to-mitigate-the-risk-of-karakurt-data-extortion-group-s-tactics-techniques-and-procedures"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group has become the new face of ransomware, taking advantage of vulnerabilities and poor encryption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Bledsoe, CEO, Theon Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magecart Serves Up Card Skimmers on Restaurant-Ordering Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180254</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/magecart-restaurant-ordering-systems/180254/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T12:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[300 restaurants and at least 50,000 payment cards compromised by two separate campaigns against MenuDrive, Harbortouch and InTouchPOS services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling the Cybersecurity Workforce Challenge With Apprentices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/tackling-the-cybersecurity-workforce-challenge-with-apprentices</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/tackling-the-cybersecurity-workforce-challenge-with-apprentices"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T00:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the announcements out of the National Cyber Workforce and Education Summit on July 19 was the 120-day Cybersecurity Apprenticeship Sprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fahmida Y. Rashid, Managing Editor, Features, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ongoing Magecart Campaign Targets Online Ordering at Local Restaurants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/magecart-online-ordering-local-restaurants</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/magecart-online-ordering-local-restaurants"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T20:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 311 local eateries have been breached through online ordering platforms MenuDrive, Harbortouch, and InTouchPOS, impacting 50K records — and counting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-Breakup, Conti Ransomware Members Remain Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/breakup-conti-ransomware-members-dangerous</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/breakup-conti-ransomware-members-dangerous"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T19:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gang's members have moved into different criminal activities, and could regroup once law-enforcement attention has simmered down a bit, researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Aims to Secure AI, Machine Learning Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/emerging-tech/startup-aims-to-secure-ai-machine-learning-development</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/emerging-tech/startup-aims-to-secure-ai-machine-learning-development"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T19:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With security experts warning against attacks on machine learning models and data, startup HiddenLayer aims to protect the neural networks powering AI-augmented products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta Exposes Passwords in Clear Text for Possible Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/okta-exposes-passwords-clear-text-theft</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/okta-exposes-passwords-clear-text-theft"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers say Okta could allow attackers to easily exfiltrate passwords, impersonate other users, and alter logs to cover their tracks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Your Cyber-Insurance Premiums Protect You in Times of War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/will-your-cyber-insurance-premiums-protect-you-in-times-of-war-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/will-your-cyber-insurance-premiums-protect-you-in-times-of-war-"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple cyber-insurance carriers have adopted act-of-war exclusions due to global political instability and are seeking to stretch the definition of war to deny coverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shimrit Tzur-David, CTO &amp; Co-founder, Secret Double Octopus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huntress Acquires Curricula for $22M to Disrupt Security Training Market, Elevate Cyber Readiness for SMB Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/huntress-acquires-curricula-for-22m-to-disrupt-security-training-market-elevate-cyber-readiness-for-smb-employees</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/huntress-acquires-curricula-for-22m-to-disrupt-security-training-market-elevate-cyber-readiness-for-smb-employees"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Curricula platform uses behavioral science with a simplified approach to train and educate users — and marks another step forward in Huntress’ mission to secure the 99%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Top MSRC 2022 Q2 Security Researchers!]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/?p=14448</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/2022/07/19/congratulations-to-the-top-msrc-2022-q2-security-researchers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the researchers recognized in this quarter’s Microsoft Researcher Recognition Program leaderboard! Thank you to everyone for your hard work and continued partnership to secure customers. The top three researchers of the 2022 Q2 Security Researcher Leaderboard are: Yuki Chen, Zhiyi Zhang, and William Söderberg! Check out the full list of researchers recognized …
  Congratulations to the Top MSRC 2022 Q2 Security Researchers! Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>msrc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released Security Advisory on MiCODUS MV720 Global Positioning System (GPS) Tracker]]></title>
        <id>17811 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/current-activity/2022/07/19/cisa-released-security-advisory-micodus-mv720-global-positioning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 19, 2022
CISA has released an Industrial Controls Systems Advisory (ICSA) detailing six vulnerabilities that were discovered in MiCODUS MV720 Global Positioning System Tracker. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities may allow a remote actor to exploit access and gain control the global positioning system tracker. These vulnerabilities could impact access to a vehicle fuel supply, vehicle control, or allow locational surveillance of vehicles in which the device is installed.
CISA encourages users and technicians to review ICS Advisory ICSA-22-200-01: MiCODUS MV720 GPS Tracker for technical details and mitigations and the Bitsight Report: Critical Vulnerabilities in Widely Used Vehicle GPS Tracker for additional information. 
 
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication Risks Discovered in Okta Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180249</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/risks-okta-sso/180249/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four newly discovered attack paths could lead to PII exposure, account takeover, even organizational data destruction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched GPS Tracker Security Bugs Threaten 1.5M Vehicles With Disruption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/iot/unpatched-gps-tracker-security-bugs-disruption</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/iot/unpatched-gps-tracker-security-bugs-disruption"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A GPS device from MiCODUS has six security bugs that could allow attackers to monitor 1.5 million vehicles that use the tracker, or even remotely disable vehicles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GhangorCloud Announces CAPE, a Next Generation Unified Compliance and Data Privacy Enforcement Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/ghangorcloud-announces-cape-tm-a-next-generation-unified-compliance-and-data-privacy-enforcement-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/ghangorcloud-announces-cape-tm-a-next-generation-unified-compliance-and-data-privacy-enforcement-solution"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New CAPE platform delivers patented intelligent automation and enforcement of consumer data privacy mandates at lowest total cost of ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enso Security Leads Industry Mission to Bring Control to Chaos With Community-Driven AppSec Map]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/enso-security-leads-industry-mission-to-bring-control-to-chaos-with-community-driven-appsec-map</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/enso-security-leads-industry-mission-to-bring-control-to-chaos-with-community-driven-appsec-map"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Builds personalization, posture scoring and enhanced market intelligence into interactive map of the application security ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Against Kubernetes-Borne Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/protecting-against-kubernetes-borne-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/protecting-against-kubernetes-borne-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The conventional wisdom that virtual container environments were somehow immune from malware and hackers has been upended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Duffin, Ransomware and Data Protection Expert, Veritas Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Supply Chain Concerns Reach C-Suite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/software-supply-chain-concerns-reach-c-suite</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/software-supply-chain-concerns-reach-c-suite"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major supply chain attacks have had a significant impact on software security awareness and decision-making, with more investment planned for monitoring attack surfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Spotlight: Issue in Accusoft ImageGear could lead to memory corruption, code execution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/accusoft-vuln-spotlight-.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/accusoft-vuln-spotlight-.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:45:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Tacheau of Cisco Talos discovered these vulnerabilities. Blog by Jon Munshaw. 
Cisco Talos recently discovered a use-after-free vulnerability in Accusoft ImageGear's PSD header processing function. 
The ImageGear library is a document-imaging developer toolkit that allows users to create, edit, annotate and convert various images. It supports more than 100 file formats such as DICOM, PDF and Microsoft Office. 
This vulnerability, TALOS-2022-1526 (CVE-2022-29465) could allow an attacker to cause a use-after-free condition by tricking the targeted user into opening a malformed .psd file in the application. The vulnerability leads to out-of-bounds heap writes, which causes memory corruption and, possibly, code execution. 
In adherence to Cisco’s vulnerability disclosure policy, Accusoft patched this issue and released an update for ImageGear.

Talos tested and confirmed Accusoft ImageGear, version 19.10, is affected by this vulnerability. 


The following Snort rules will detect exploitation attempts against this vulnerability: 60228 and 60229. Additional rules may be released in the future and current rules are subject to change, pending additional vulnerability information. For the most current rule information, please refer to your Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center or Snort.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cisco Talos Intelligence Group - Comprehensive Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trojanized Password Crackers Targeting Industrial Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/attackers-targeting-industrial-systems-with-trojanized-password-crackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/attackers-targeting-industrial-systems-with-trojanized-password-crackers"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T22:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tools purporting to help organizations recover lost passwords for PLCs are really droppers for malware targeting industrial control systems, vendor says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retbleed Fixed in Linux Kernel, Patch Delayed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/retbleed-fixed-in-linux-kernel-patch-delayed</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/retbleed-fixed-in-linux-kernel-patch-delayed"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T22:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds says Retbleed has been addressed in the Linux kernel, but code complexity means the release will be delayed by a week to give more time for testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI: Beware of Scam Cryptocurrency Investment Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/fbi-beware-of-scam-crypto-investment-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/fbi-beware-of-scam-crypto-investment-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement estimates campaign has already bilked cryptocurrency investors out of $42.7 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Page Builder Plug-in  Under Attack, Can't Be Patched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/wordpress-page-builder-addons-under-attack-cant-be-patched</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/wordpress-page-builder-addons-under-attack-cant-be-patched"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing campaign is actively targeting the vulnerability in the Kaswara Modern WPBakery Page Builder Addon, which is still installed on up to 8,000 sites, security analysts warn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name That Toon: Modern-Day Fable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/name-that-toon-modern-day-fable</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/name-that-toon-modern-day-fable"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling creative? Submit your caption and our panel of experts will reward the winner with a $25 Amazon gift card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Klossner, Cartoonist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SA45038 - CVE-2022-23852 - Expat (aka libexpat) before 2.4.4 has a signed integer overflow in XML_GetBuffer, for configurations with a nonzero XML_CONTEXT_BYTES]]></title>
        <id>CVE-2022-23852-Expat-aka-libexpat-before-2-4-4-has-a-signed-integer-overflow-in-XML-GetBuffer-for-configurations-with-a-nonzero-XML-CONTEXT-BYTES</id>
        <link href="https://kb.pulsesecure.net/articles/Pulse_Security_Advisories/CVE-2022-23852-Expat-aka-libexpat-before-2-4-4-has-a-signed-integer-overflow-in-XML-GetBuffer-for-configurations-with-a-nonzero-XML-CONTEXT-BYTES"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Public KB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Attempts Flag as Payments Also Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-attempts-flag-as-payments-also-decline</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-attempts-flag-as-payments-also-decline"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telecom and business services see the highest level of attacks, but the two most common ransomware families, which continue to be LockBit and Conti, are seen less often.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Guardrails for Autonomic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/building-guardrails-for-autonomic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/building-guardrails-for-autonomic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI's potential for automating security has promise, but there are miles to go in establishing decision-making boundaries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sounil Yu, CISO and Head of Research, JupiterOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out for User Impersonation in Low-Code/No-Code Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/watch-out-for-user-impersonation-in-low-code-no-code-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/watch-out-for-user-impersonation-in-low-code-no-code-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How a well-meaning employee could unwittingly share their identity with other users, causing a whole range of problems across IT, security, and the business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Bargury, CTO &amp; Co-Founder, Zenity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitigation for Azure Storage SDK Client-Side Encryption Padding Oracle Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/?p=14435</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/2022/07/18/mitigation-for-azure-storage-sdk-client-side-encryption-padding-oracle-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary: Google informed Microsoft under Coordinated Vulnerability Disclosure (CVD) of a padding oracle vulnerability that may affect customers using Azure Storage SDK (for Python, .NET, Java) client-side encryption (CVE-2022-30187). To mitigate this vulnerability, we released a new General Availability (GA) version of the Azure Storage SDK client-side encryption feature (v2) on July 12, 2022. Microsoft …
  Mitigation for Azure Storage SDK Client-Side Encryption Padding Oracle Vulnerability Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>msrc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Urges Patch of Exploited Windows 11 Bug by Aug. 2]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180235</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/cisa-urges-patch-11-bug/180235/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feds urge U.S. agencies to patch a Microsoft July Patch Tuesday 2022 bug that is being exploited in the wild by August 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Threatpost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netwrix Auditor Bug Could Lead to Active Directory Domain Compromise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/netwrix-auditor-bug-could-lead-to-active-directory-domain-compromise</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/netwrix-auditor-bug-could-lead-to-active-directory-domain-compromise"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT asset tracker and auditor software has a critical issue with insecure object deserialization that could allow threat actors to execute code, researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Risks of Employees Going on a 'Hybrid Holiday'?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-ask-the-experts/what-are-the-risks-of-employees-going-on-a-hybrid-holiday-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-ask-the-experts/what-are-the-risks-of-employees-going-on-a-hybrid-holiday-"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more employees plan on taking longer holidays and working remotely from the destination for part of that time, organizations have to consider the risks. Like Wi-Fi networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Ayers, Vice President of Product, Advanced Detection &amp; Response, Optiv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Could Dupe Developers into Downloading Malicious Code From GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/how-attackers-could-dupe-developers-into-downloading-malicious-code-from-github</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/how-attackers-could-dupe-developers-into-downloading-malicious-code-from-github"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers need to be cautious about whom they trust on GitHub because it's easy to establish fake credibility on the platform, security vendor warns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-CIA Programmer Found Guilty of Stealing Vault 7 Data, Giving It to Wikileaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/cia-programmer-guilty-of-stealing-vault-7-data-giving-it-to-wikileaks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/cia-programmer-guilty-of-stealing-vault-7-data-giving-it-to-wikileaks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Schulte has been convicted for his role in the Vault 7 Wikileaks data dump that exposed invasive US cyber intelligence tactics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandworm APT Trolls Researchers on Its Trail as It Targets Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/sandworm-apt-trolls-researchers-on-its-trail-while-it-targets-ukraine</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/sandworm-apt-trolls-researchers-on-its-trail-while-it-targets-ukraine"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers who helped thwart the Russian nation-state group's recent attack on Ukraine's power supply will disclose at Black Hat USA what they found while reverse-engineering the powerful Industroyer2 malware used by the powerful hacking team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly Jackson Higgins, Editor-in-Chief, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Hackers Create Fake Personas for Social Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/how-hackers-create-fake-personas-for-social-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/how-hackers-create-fake-personas-for-social-engineering"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And some ways to up your game for identifying fabricated online profiles of people who don't exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Hammond, Senior Security Researcher, Huntress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox Secures $75 Million in Growth Funding From Carrick Capital Partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/bishop-fox-secures-75-million-in-growth-funding-from-carrick-capital-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/bishop-fox-secures-75-million-in-growth-funding-from-carrick-capital-partners"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T22:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive security leader continues to defy market and economic trends with record growth and recognized innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DHS Review Board Deems Log4j an 'Endemic' Cyber Threat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/dhs-review-board-deems-log4j-an-endemic-cyber-threat</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/dhs-review-board-deems-log4j-an-endemic-cyber-threat"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability will remain a "significant" threat for years to come and highlighted the need for more public and private sector support for open source software ecosystem, Cyber Safety Review Board says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Phishing Kit Hijacks WordPress Sites for PayPal Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/new-phishing-kit-hijacks-wordpress-sites-for-paypal-scam</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/new-phishing-kit-hijacks-wordpress-sites-for-paypal-scam"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers use scam security checks to steal victims' government documents, photos, banking information, and email passwords, researchers warn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scribe Security Releases Code Integrity Validator Alongside Github Security Open Source Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/scribe-security-releases-code-integrity-validator-alongside-github-security-open-source-project</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/scribe-security-releases-code-integrity-validator-alongside-github-security-open-source-project"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers can now rest assured that the code they are using, as well as their GitHub accounts, are safe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AEI HorizonX Ventures Joins Shift5 Series B Funding Round]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/aei-horizonx-ventures-joins-shift5-series-b-funding-round</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/aei-horizonx-ventures-joins-shift5-series-b-funding-round"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment bolsters Shift5’s traction within commercial aerospace and defense industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data of Nearly 2M Patients Exposed in Ransomware Attack on Healthcare Debt Collection Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/nearly-2m-patients-affected-in-data-breach-of-healthcare-debt-collection-firm</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/nearly-2m-patients-affected-in-data-breach-of-healthcare-debt-collection-firm"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Professional Finance Company (PFC) was hit in February 2022 by a ransomware attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Cryptocurrency's Crash Causing Headaches for Ransomware Gangs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/is-cryptocurrency-s-crash-causing-headaches-for-ransomware-gangs-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/is-cryptocurrency-s-crash-causing-headaches-for-ransomware-gangs-"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is down more than 70% from its highs late last year, causing disruptions for cybercriminals and the underground exchanges that fuel the dark markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Spotlight: Use-after-free condition in Google Chrome WebGPU]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/chrome-web-gpu-useafterfree.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/chrome-web-gpu-useafterfree.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:22:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Piotr Bania of Cisco Talos discovered this vulnerability. Blog by Jon Munshaw. 
Cisco Talos recently discovered an exploitable use-after-free vulnerability in Google Chrome’s WebGPU standard.  
Google Chrome is a cross-platform web browser — and Chromium is the open-source version of the browser that both Google and other software developers use as the basis to build their browsers, as well. This specific vulnerability exists in WebGPU, which is a JavaScript API for processing accelerated 3-D graphics and other functions in the browser. 
TALOS-2022-1508 (CVE-2022-2399) occurs if the user opens a specially crafted web page in Chrome. That page could trigger a use-after-free condition in the application, which an attacker could then use to manipulate the browser in additional ways.  

Cisco Talos worked with Google to ensure that this issue is resolved and an update is available for affected customers, all in adherence to Cisco’s vulnerability disclosure policy. 
Users are encouraged to update these affected products as soon as possible: Google Chrome, version 102.0.4956.0 (64-bit) and 99.0.4844.82 (64-bit). Talos tested and confirmed these versions of Chrome could be exploited by this vulnerability. 


The following Snort rules will detect exploitation attempts against this vulnerability: 59448 and 59449. Additional rules may be released in the future and current rules are subject to change, pending additional vulnerability information. For the most current rule information, please refer to your Firepower Management Center or Snort.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cisco Talos Intelligence Group - Comprehensive Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual CISOs Are the Best Defense Against Accelerating Cyber-Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/virtual-cisos-are-the-best-defense-against-accelerating-cyber-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/virtual-cisos-are-the-best-defense-against-accelerating-cyber-risks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A poor, permanent hire can be a very expensive error, whereas a mis-hire on a virtual CISO can be rapidly corrected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Tiller, Global CISO, Nash Squared and Harvey Nash USA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Generation of Threat Detection Will Require Both Human and Machine Expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/the-cyber-future/the-next-generation-of-threat-detection-will-require-both-human-and-machine-expertise</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/the-cyber-future/the-next-generation-of-threat-detection-will-require-both-human-and-machine-expertise"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T13:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be truly effective, threat detection and response need to combine the strengths of people and technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kumar Saurabh, CEO and Co-Founder, LogicHub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Breaches Linked to Ransomware Declined in Q2 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/data-breaches-linked-to-ransomware-declined-in-q2-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/data-breaches-linked-to-ransomware-declined-in-q2-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T13:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing retained its place as the top root cause of data compromises, according to new data from the Identity Theft Resource Center (ITRC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Devise New Speculative Execution Attacks Against Some Intel, AMD CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/researchers-devise-new-speculative-execution-attacks-against-some-intel-amd-cpus</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/researchers-devise-new-speculative-execution-attacks-against-some-intel-amd-cpus"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Retbleed" bypasses a commonly used mechanism for protecting against a certain kind of side-channel attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyberRatings.org Issues AAA Rating on Forcepoint's Cloud Network Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cyberratings-org-issues-aaa-rating-on-forcepoint-s-cloud-network-firewall</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cyberratings-org-issues-aaa-rating-on-forcepoint-s-cloud-network-firewall"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T21:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forcepoint's test results are second in a series of publications on this new technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Financial Institutions Overly Complacent About Current Authentication Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/report-financial-institutions-overly-complacent-about-current-authentication-methods</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/report-financial-institutions-overly-complacent-about-current-authentication-methods"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T21:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research report finds most financial organizations have experienced a breach due to an authentication weakness, yet only a third took action]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Spotlight: Adobe Acrobat DC use-after-free issues could lead to arbitrary code execution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/vulnerability-spotlight-adobe-acrobat.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2022/07/vulnerability-spotlight-adobe-acrobat.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T15:49:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aleksandar Nikolic of Cisco Talos discovered these vulnerabilities. Blog by Jon Munshaw. 
Cisco Talos recently discovered two use-after-free vulnerabilities in Adobe Acrobat Reader DC that could allow an attacker to eventually gain the ability to execute arbitrary code.  
Acrobat is one of the most popular PDF reader software options available currently. It includes the ability to read and process JavaScript to give PDFs greater interactivity and customization options for users. This vulnerability exists in the way Acrobat Reader processes JavaScript.  

TALOS-2022-1516 (CVE-2022-34221) is a type confusion vulnerability that is triggered if the user opens a PDF with specially crafted, malicious JavaScript embedded. Object misuse can cause memory corruption, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. TALOS-2022-1525 (CVE-2022-34230) can trigger the reuse of a freed object, which can ultimately result in arbitrary code execution, as well.

Cisco Talos worked with Adobe to ensure that these issues are resolved and an update is available for affected customers, all in adherence to Cisco’s vulnerability disclosure policy. 


Users are advised to update the following software, which is tested and confirmed to be affected by these vulnerabilities: Adobe Acrobat Reader, version 2022.001.20085.  


The following Snort rules will detect exploitation attempts against this vulnerability: 59644, 59645, 59942 and 59943. Additional rules may be released in the future and current rules are subject to change, pending additional vulnerability information. For the most current rule information, please refer to your Cisco Secure Firewall management center or Snort.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cisco Talos Intelligence Group - Comprehensive Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Hands-on Deck: A Whole-of-Society Approach for Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/?p=14404</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/2022/07/13/all-hands-on-deck-a-whole-of-society-approach-for-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T14:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The morning of June 9th, I was driving over the Golden Gate Bridge into San Francisco with my family. While crossing the bridge my children shared some facts about this modern engineering marvel. Each day, approx. 100,000 vehicles travel over the bridge deck, which weighs a staggering 150,000 tons, and is suspended by 250 pairs …
  All Hands-on Deck: A Whole-of-Society Approach for Cybersecurity Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhilasha Bhargav-Spantzel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large-Scale Phishing Campaign Bypasses MFA]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180212</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/large-scale-hishing-bypasses-mfa/180212/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T11:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers used adversary-in-the-middle attacks to steal passwords, hijack sign-in sessions and skip authentication and then use victim mailboxes to launch BEC attacks against other targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Mitigates Azure Site Recovery Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/?p=14395</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/2022/07/12/microsoft-mitigates-azure-site-recovery-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary: Microsoft recently mitigated a set of vulnerabilities in Azure Site Recovery (ASR) and released fixes today, July 12, as part of our regular Update Tuesday cycle. These vulnerabilities affect all ASR on-premises customers using a VMware/Physical to Azure scenario and are fixed in the latest ASR 9.49 release. We recommend customers update to the …
  Microsoft Mitigates Azure Site Recovery Vulnerabilities Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>msrc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Callback’ Phishing Campaign Impersonates Security Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180182</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/callback-phishing-security-firms/180182/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T11:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victims instructed to make a phone call that will direct them to a link for downloading malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack Allows Drone Takeover Via ‘ExpressLRS’ Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://kasperskycontenthub.com/threatpost-global/?p=180133</id>
        <link href="https://threatpost.com/drone-hack-expresslrs-hijacked/180133/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T11:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radio control system for drones is vulnerable to remote takeover, thanks to a weakness in the mechanism that binds transmitter and receiver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AA22-187A: North Korean State-Sponsored Cyber Actors Use Maui Ransomware to Target the Healthcare and Public Health Sector]]></title>
        <id>17768 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/alerts/aa22-187a"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: July 6, 2022 | Last revised: July 7, 2022
Summary
The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), and the Department of the Treasury (Treasury) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) to provide information on Maui ransomware, which has been used by North Korean state-sponsored cyber actors since at least May 2021 to target Healthcare and Public Health (HPH) Sector organizations.
This joint CSA provides information—including tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) and indicators of compromise (IOCs)—on Maui ransomware obtained from FBI incident response activities and industry analysis of a Maui sample. The FBI, CISA, and Treasury urge HPH Sector organizations as well as other critical infrastructur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>